[Music]
[音乐]
这部影片是关于
[Music]
this video is about the development of
弹出的书从
始于1890年代
this video is about the development of
pop-up books looking at them from the
20世纪中叶，我将
看这一系列的书和
pop-up books looking at them from the
very beginnings in the 1890s through to
解释哪些教程与
机制我们的设计
very beginnings in the 1890s through to
the middle of the 20th century I'll be
看着，所以这是我第一个
喜欢看这是国际
the middle of the 20th century I'll be
looking at this range of books and
Lothar meg和Orpha的马戏团，这是
从1887年开始
looking at this range of books and
explaining which tutorials relate to the
解释的平行四边形
教程5是整个系列
explaining which tutorials relate to the
mechanisms the designs that we're
你可以看到它们都是平行四边形
在这部影片的结尾，我将设定
mechanisms the designs that we're
looking at so this is the first one I'd
整个事情，你可以看到它
充满荣耀，下一本书
looking at so this is the first one I'd
like to look at this is International
也是Lothar meg和Orpha的
洋娃娃的房子，这是从1890年代开始的
like to look at this is International
circus by Lothar meg and Orpha this is
认为所有由平行四边形制成
教程5这是他们的工作方式
circus by Lothar meg and Orpha this is
from 1887 it's all made with
平行四边形是整件事吗
打开成一个4英尺长的蔓延
from 1887 it's all made with
parallelograms which are explained in
尽头的娃娃屋
我将对其进行设置，以便您可以看到
parallelograms which are explained in
tutorial 5 it's a whole series of these
它的全部荣耀在于整个模型
四英尺是由一系列的
tutorial 5 it's a whole series of these
you can see they're all parallelograms
这些都是教程的平行四边形
5，最后一个我想给你看
you can see they're all parallelograms
and at the end of this video I'll set
来自meg和Orpha是这个城市公园
是从1890年开始的，不是真正的弹出式窗口
and at the end of this video I'll set
the whole thing up and you can see it in
更像是一个模型
六角琴与其中许多
the whole thing up and you can see it in
it's in all its glory and the next book
框架各不相同，您可以安排
在各种各样的住宿中
it's in all its glory and the next book
also by Lothar meg and Orpha is the
视频的结尾，我还要设置
这样您就可以看到可能性
also by Lothar meg and Orpha is the
doll's house this is from the 1890s I
因为最后真的很有趣
我想从19日开始向你展示
doll's house this is from the 1890s I
think all made with parallelograms
这是本世纪最古老的书
收集它的窥视秀图片
think all made with parallelograms
tutorial 5 this is how they work these
嵌套Nesta弹出窗口不是很好
一切都基于
tutorial 5 this is how they work these
are the parallelograms the whole thing
平行四边形，这是一个例子
他们没有以使
are the parallelograms the whole thing
opens up into a 4 foot long spread a
整个结构都是刚性的，所以他们做到了
如果你看着它，实际上会晃动
opens up into a 4 foot long spread a
doll's house again at the end of the
最后，您可以看到它实际上是
只是一系列支柱
doll's house again at the end of the
tutorials I'll set it up so you can see
支撑这些不同的层
这是1894年的欧内斯特·屈膝，所以
tutorials I'll set it up so you can see
it in all its glory the whole model or
19世纪真正的波普尔开始于
1928年着这本书《每日快报》
it in all its glory the whole model or
four feet is made of a whole series of
儿童年度，由
西奥多·布朗（Theodore brown），路易莎（Louisa）出版
four feet is made of a whole series of
these all parallelograms that's tutorial
道和西奥多·布朗真的是
弹出的天才，所有弹出的
these all parallelograms that's tutorial
5 and the last one I want to show you
您会发现这些日子源于
西奥多（Theodore）发明的设计
5 and the last one I want to show you
from meg and Orpha is the city park this
棕色，这是第一个弹出窗口
模仿这所房子，这些书是
from meg and Orpha is the city park this
is from 1890 it's not a true pop-up this
描述为所有彩色图片
以模型形式出现，所以他们没有
is from 1890 it's not a true pop-up this
is more of a model that it unfolds in a
在这一点上发明了弹出这个词
房子基本上是敞开的
is more of a model that it unfolds in a
concertina with however many of these
这是教程18的后面
这个屏幕是锯齿形的
concertina with however many of these
frames all different and you can arrange
折叠教程20本书的下一个
我想给你看这张床
frames all different and you can arrange
it in all sorts of accommodations so at
基于盒形教程14
盒子的钥匙是
it in all sorts of accommodations so at
the end of the video I'll also set this
中间的支柱从
推开盒子盖子的中心
the end of the video I'll also set this
up so you can see the possibilities
在这种情况下是床的顶部
然后这个屏幕在后面
up so you can see the possibilities
because it it really is fun the last
另一个之字形折叠教程20因此
这真的是西奥多的天才吗
because it it really is fun the last
book I'd like to show you from the 19th
布朗，他从那开始
打开顶部的形状，然后他继续前进
book I'd like to show you from the 19th
century is it's the oldest book in my
这个盒子的形状实际上是
真正复杂的机制
century is it's the oldest book in my
collection it's peepshow pictures by
我们这里是一个，这是第一个V形折叠
V折叠这是教程2，
collection it's peepshow pictures by
ernest Nesta the pop-up isn't very
这很好奇他有这些奇怪的地方
后面的想法是
ernest Nesta the pop-up isn't very
sophisticated it's all based on
打开和关闭它会使耳朵进入
下来，但实际上我认为这是
sophisticated it's all based on
parallelograms and here's an example
有点复杂一点
但是无论如何，这确实是第一个
parallelograms and here's an example
they're not held in a way that makes the
V折
所以当我们在这里，我只会告诉你
they're not held in a way that makes the
whole structure rigid so they do
背面，你真的知道
一团糟，你知道那是原始的
whole structure rigid so they do
actually rock around if you look at it
早弹出他显然只是在玩
试图获得他的影响
actually rock around if you look at it
end on you can see that it's actually
想要，但这不是真的
令人满意，这是最后一个
end on you can see that it's actually
just a series of pillars that are
书是这个，这又是这个
将这个婴儿在浴缸中抚平，然后
just a series of pillars that are
holding up these different layers so
非常非常简单的V形折叠，这是这个
是一个锐角的教程
holding up these different layers so
this is 1894 Ernest kneestr so that's
v折叠默认指向前方，并且
整个v形折叠随着
this is 1894 Ernest kneestr so that's
the 19th century true popper began in
页面关闭，这只手臂只是一个襟翼
确实有效，这是您知道的很不寻常
the 19th century true popper began in
1928 with this book The Daily Express
但是随着本书的开闭，是的
所以这是第一本弹出书
1928 with this book The Daily Express
children's annual this was designed by
他们会表达孩子们的丹尼尔数
我也带来了一个
children's annual this was designed by
Theodore brown and published by Louisa
快递儿童年度三号
那是大概在1929年之后的一年
Theodore brown and published by Louisa
Road and Theodore Brown is really the
认为这是第一个，所以他是
变得更加奢侈，这是
Road and Theodore Brown is really the
genius behind pop up and all pop up that
再次是费奥多·布朗（Fyodor Brown）的发明
路易莎·罗斯（Louisa Rose）出版物，我们在这里
genius behind pop up and all pop up that
you see these days has its roots in the
宝塔的主体是
顶部形状是教程18，它是
you see these days has its roots in the
designs developed invented by Theodore
不是盒子
没有什么推高中间
designs developed invented by Theodore
brown so this is the very first pop-up
然后这些是平行四边形
它是教程五和
brown so this is the very first pop-up
model this house these books were
整个平行四边形阵列
是平行折叠教程六，不是
model this house these books were
described as all the colored pictures
实际上是平行四边形，但所有
折叠在一起，它们是平行的，所以
described as all the colored pictures
rise up in model form so they hadn't
你有一个很有趣的设计
这个宝塔在中间然后
rise up in model form so they hadn't
invented the word pop up at this point
这些平行四边形，他把所有
你们知道有趣的网关
invented the word pop up at this point
the house is basically an open top shape
树木在这里，我们架起了一座桥梁
这是这里的盛大
the house is basically an open top shape
which is tutorial 18 and at the back
瓷砖与帕科达的入口
在后面的地板上，这里有一点
which is tutorial 18 and at the back
this screen of trees this is a zigzag
人力车所以很多细节你都可以
看看设计是如何发展的
this screen of trees this is a zigzag
fold tutorial 20 next one in this book
进展，所以这仍然是西奥多
布朗·西奥多·布朗的发明
fold tutorial 20 next one in this book
that I'd like to show you this bed this
路易莎排出版，所以他们
团队合作
that I'd like to show you this bed this
is based on the box shape tutorial 14
本书的下一个是
相当惊人的传播这是一朵花
is based on the box shape tutorial 14
and the key for the box is there's a
童话，这一切都是基于钝角
角度v型折叠，即教程三，
and the key for the box is there's a
pillar in the middle rising up from the
然后增加了两个基本的折痕
形状
pillar in the middle rising up from the
center that pushes up the lid of the box
那是教程七，非常
复杂的弹出窗口，希望如此
center that pushes up the lid of the box
which in this case is the top of the bed
在以后的教程中，我将能够
充分说明并告诉您如何
which in this case is the top of the bed
and then this screen at the back that's
做到了，但我认为这只是一个
出色的设计，所以只是出于兴趣
and then this screen at the back that's
another zigzag fold tutorial 20 so this
我会告诉你后面你可以看到的
这是钝角v形，所以
another zigzag fold tutorial 20 so this
is this is really genius of Theodore
在页面上指向V形折叠，但实际上
向后倾斜，您可能想要
is this is really genius of Theodore
Brown he the way he started with that
以全部方式查看整个事情
很难看到实际上是什么
Brown he the way he started with that
open top shape then he's moved on to
继续下去，如果你在这里看
需要进一步研究这个模型
open top shape then he's moved on to
this box shape which is actually a
这本书的下一个是
锐角v型折叠教程
this box shape which is actually a
really sophisticated mechanism the next
这是一个之字形故障教程20
该日志中有一个平行折叠
really sophisticated mechanism the next
one here we are this is the first V fold
中间是教程六和颜色
事情是当你打开
one here we are this is the first V fold
so that V folds this is tutorial 2 and
关闭它的V形折叠动作是
像这样移动，之字形折叠
so that V folds this is tutorial 2 and
this is quite curious he's got these odd
配置方式意味着您已经
有一些东西在那里，所以当你打开和
this is quite curious he's got these odd
bits at the back the idea is that as you
关闭你实际上得到的书
模型锯日志相当令人愉快
bits at the back the idea is that as you
open and close it it makes the ears come
实际上，这个弹出窗口实际上正在
整个领域再上一个台阶，因为
open and close it it makes the ears come
down but really in my opinion it's a
现在它正在成为一种工作模式
不仅仅是3D插图
down but really in my opinion it's a
little bit over complicated a bit enough
我想指出的是
会标的这是西奥多
little bit over complicated a bit enough
but anyway this this is really the first
布朗设计师真的是发明家
所有弹出式设计之父，
but anyway this this is really the first
V fold
那么这本书的最后一个是
在非常非凡的盛会
V fold
so while we're at it I'll just show you
马戏团都是基于这个帐篷
这是一个对称的折叠教程六
so while we're at it I'll just show you
the back of this and you know it really
你实际上可以看到你知道什么时候
这些书是
the back of this and you know it really
is a mess it's you know it's it's crude
有时候，制造商就是
和平工作，他们有点傻
is a mess it's you know it's it's crude
early pop up he's obviously just playing
所以在这里你可以看到这个标记表明它是
是数字L这是此选项卡的位置
early pop up he's obviously just playing
around trying to get the effects he
本来应该坚持，但实际上
事实上，无论谁使它卡住了一点
around trying to get the effects he
wants but it that's not really
更接近脊椎，这意味着
然后这边也更靠近
wants but it that's not really
satisfactory and the last one from this
脊柱意味着整个帐篷
没有尽可能多地打开
satisfactory and the last one from this
book is this one this again this is a
已经做了，如果你发现
这本书的另一本《每日快报》
book is this one this again this is a
v-fold raising this baby in the bath and
孩子们每年第三名
会在里面找到一个更好的帐篷，但是
v-fold raising this baby in the bath and
very very simple v-fold so this is this
无论如何，这是一个很好的
你可以看的漂亮的小模型
very very simple v-fold so this is this
is tutorial to it's an acute angle
通过那里的门，你可以看到
帐篷里发生的事情
is tutorial to it's an acute angle
v-folds default pointing forwards and
我只是在后面照亮
你可能会看到拳击比赛，所以
v-folds default pointing forwards and
the whole v-fold comes forward as the
待售Express儿童系列
他们实际上是年度第三
the whole v-fold comes forward as the
page closes this arm is just a flap it
这些日常表达儿童中的五个
年，然后路易莎·罗（Louisa Rowe）离开了
page closes this arm is just a flap it
does work it's a you know fairly unusual
离开《每日快报》自己建立
公司称为Strand出版物和
does work it's a you know fairly unusual
but yeah as as the book opens and closes
然后他们继续生产一个整体
巴卡诺系列丛书，所以我回来了
so this is the very first pop-up book
这是我们今年第三的照片
以模型形式出现，这是从周围
so this is the very first pop-up book
they'll express children's Daniel number
1935年，在这里我们可以看到他们真的
通过3D弹出框大步向前
they'll express children's Daniel number
one I've also brought along they'll
插图，我认为这是真的
与两位舞者的美女模特
one I've also brought along they'll
Express children's annual number three
前面，然后整个聚会
在他们的背后和教程
Express children's annual number three
this was the year after probably 1929 I
盖天，如果您
看着它结束，你会看到有一个
this was the year after probably 1929 I
think here's the first one so he's
中间的支柱上升上升
他的肩膀顶是
think here's the first one so he's
getting a bit more extravagant this is
实际上是盒子的盖子，然后
手臂移动的方式也是
getting a bit more extravagant this is
again it's Fyodor Brown's invention
聪明的纸张力学，我会
在另一个教程中介绍
again it's Fyodor Brown's invention
Louisa Rose publication and here we've
这个数字是用尖的V制成的
折叠教程三，以便您打开并
Louisa Rose publication and here we've
got the main body of the pagoda is an
关闭它
她实际上稍微偏向
got the main body of the pagoda is an
open top shape which is tutorial 18 it's
其他数字，所以他们有不同
动作非常聪明
open top shape which is tutorial 18 it's
not a box
所以这件在后面的就是全部
教程五的平行四边形和
not a box
there's nothing pushing up the middle
实际上是由这些碎片引起的
这里有一个这里有一个
there's nothing pushing up the middle
and then these are parallelograms coming
在这里拉起来这是
不对称的平行折叠
and then these are parallelograms coming
off it which are tutorial five and the
本教程确实是一个相当
有很多东西的复杂模型
off it which are tutorial five and the
whole array of parallelograms and this
进行非常巧妙的分钟设计
本书的下一个是这个
whole array of parallelograms and this
is parallel fold tutorial six it's not
低音提琴演奏者，这一切都基于
在盒子教程14上，实际上是
is parallel fold tutorial six it's not
actually a parallelogram but all the
盒子上的变化，因为
中间有一个支柱
actually a parallelogram but all the
folds in it they're parallel so it's
两个，但效果相同，因为
顶部只有一个盖子，
folds in it they're parallel so it's
quite an interesting design you've got
聪明的东西在这里，盒子需要一个
最终的那一块
quite an interesting design you've got
this pagoda in the middle and then with
保持整个形状是刚性的
他用它来使弓移动的情况下
this pagoda in the middle and then with
these parallelograms he's raising up all
整个乐器都很聪明
他内置的设计
these parallelograms he's raising up all
sorts of you know interesting gateways
鼠标的小块
打开和关闭，所以我认为这有点
sorts of you know interesting gateways
and trees here we've got a bridge over
尝试走得更远
付出很少的努力
and trees here we've got a bridge over
this stream here this is the grand
效果，然后我们有了这些腿
这些平行四边形
this stream here this is the grand
entrance to the pakoda with the tile
你可以看看它的结尾，你可以看到
它们是盒子引起的平行四边形
entrance to the pakoda with the tile
floor behind and here there's a little
平行四边形教程五顶
一半都在动臂，一切
floor behind and here there's a little
rickshaw so yeah a lot of detail you can
非常聪明，有点失望
下半部那不是你
rickshaw so yeah a lot of detail you can
see how the designs are developing as it
不了解出色的视觉效果和最后一个
这本书里的戏剧是全部
see how the designs are developing as it
progresses so this is still Theodore
教程14实际上是两个盒子
放在一个盒子里，放在肩膀上
progresses so this is still Theodore
Brown Theodore Browns inventions
在教程中添加了额外的折痕
七，这是这部戏，所以
Brown Theodore Browns inventions
Louisa row publishing so they they were
所有这些书路易丝欧元和
他们正在工作的西奥多·布朗
Louisa row publishing so they they were
working as a team
伦敦，他们启发了一个叫
Harold Lentz在美国和美国工作
working as a team
and the next one in this book is this
1932年这本书出品了皮诺曹
和质量
and the next one in this book is this
quite an amazing spread this is a flower
图形确实更难
别人有点模糊，我想你
quite an amazing spread this is a flower
fairy this is all based on the obtuse
称之为主体，这是一个平行
折叠金字塔，这是教程21，
fairy this is all based on the obtuse
angle v-fold that is tutorial three and
你可以看到皮诺曹自己
粘在脊椎上，与
angle v-fold that is tutorial three and
then it's adding extra creases two basic
金字塔，所以当您打开和关闭它
他的头从上面放大
then it's adding extra creases two basic
shapes
设计非常聪明，如果
我们把它转过来，你可以看看
shapes
that's tutorial seven it's a very
后面，您可以看到耳机的状态
卡在脊椎上，以便您打开并
that's tutorial seven it's a very
sophisticated pop-up this and hopefully
关闭它，使头部通过
我要展示的下一个金字塔
sophisticated pop-up this and hopefully
in a future tutorial I'll be able to
这本书里的你是这个，我会说这个
设计是从
in a future tutorial I'll be able to
explain it fully and show you how to
我第一个给你看了西奥多
布朗在每日快递中的设计
explain it fully and show you how to
make it but I think it's just a
儿童年度第一房子
是一个开放的形状，这是教程
make it but I think it's just a
brilliant design so just out of interest
18然后这些边
用45度折叠起来
brilliant design so just out of interest
I'll show you the back you can see that
飞机和45度折是
教程23仙女这是最
I'll show you the back you can see that
this is the obtuse angle v-fold so it's
简单的弹出窗口，真的，这是一个
并行文件夹的形式就是这样
this is the obtuse angle v-fold so it's
a v-fold pointing up the page but really
你会看到它是一张普通纸
这已经被分开了一点
a v-fold pointing up the page but really
leaning backwards and you might want to
每侧各有两个标签
然后它们平行于
leaning backwards and you might want to
see the whole thing the way it all works
每个脊柱仅几毫米
侧面，使轮渡稳定
see the whole thing the way it all works
it's very hard to see what's actually
让她站起来
房子和我要展示的最后一个
it's very hard to see what's actually
going on if you look in under here so I
你在这本书中就是这个
这条鱼任命还折这
going on if you look in under here so I
need to investigate this model some more
是观点的错
这些是教程三，然后这
need to investigate this model some more
and the next one in this book this is an
实际上是一个拱门，有几个
拱门，所以在教程34中，然后
and the next one in this book this is an
acute angle v-fold tutorial too and then
这些正在添加小的3D片段
教程八，然后在这里
acute angle v-fold tutorial too and then
this is a zigzag fault tutorial 20
我们有匹诺曹，这是另一个
折叠
this is a zigzag fault tutorial 20
there's a parallel fold this log in the
切成小拱形并被
被鱼吃掉作为页面
there's a parallel fold this log in the
middle that's tutorial six and the color
打开可能鱼落了
不幸的是还有一块
middle that's tutorial six and the color
thing about this is as you open and
鱼，这已经迷路了
这本书是1932年写的，所以你知道
thing about this is as you open and
close it the action of the v-fold is to
一百岁了
零零碎碎
close it the action of the v-fold is to
move like that and the zigzag folds the
不幸的是，但是不错的图形和
我要向您展示的最后一个
move like that and the zigzag folds the
way it's being configured means you've
1930年代也是一本蓝丝带的书
由Harold Lentz设计，这是
way it's being configured means you've
got some gives there so as you open and
1934年的一个，所以这是Goldilocks，
他们三只熊的蓝丝带书
got some gives there so as you open and
close the book you actually get the
发明了术语pop up，所以这是
出现的单词首先出现的位置
close the book you actually get the
model sawing the log is rather pleasing
他们不需要这些很棒的书
弹出窗口是什么灯
model sawing the log is rather pleasing
really this pop-up is actually taking
人，所以你得到这些，有一个
这些书的整个系列
really this pop-up is actually taking
the whole field to another level because
相当苗条，每个人都有三个
弹出窗口，但我只显示
the whole field to another level because
now it's becoming a working model rather
您一个人，所以这里是Goldilocks
背负熊主体
now it's becoming a working model rather
than just a 3d illustration the last
房子的这是平行的折叠
对称的平行折叠
than just a 3d illustration the last
thing I'd like to point out is this
教程六这是v折叠教程
增加折痕，使您的头部增加
thing I'd like to point out is this
little T be monogrammed this is Theodore
折痕使您感到复杂
屋顶，它们都是多余的折痕
little T be monogrammed this is Theodore
Brown the designer the inventor really
是教程七，这是一个
平行四边形，但它的方式
Brown the designer the inventor really
the the father of all pop-up designs and
提出这只是一个聪明的
玩耍，如果你想做
the the father of all pop-up designs and
then the last one in this book this is
只是尝试一下就很容易
找到确实有效的东西
then the last one in this book this is
quite extraordinary extravaganza at the
没有关于此的特定教程
这是城市公园的传真
quite extraordinary extravaganza at the
circus it's all based on this the tent
从大约1890年由Lothal mega设计
海豚六角琴与14帧与
circus it's all based on this the tent
here is a symmetrical fold tutorial six
所有这些生命的晕影
1890年，他在德国工作
here is a symmetrical fold tutorial six
and you can actually see you know when
各种迷人的细节
并没有真正弹出3D
and you can actually see you know when
these books were made
Enix
是的，其他东西可爱的孩子们
these books were made
sometimes the manufacturers that was all
故事真的是这是娃娃屋
洛萨·梅格（Lothar meg）和奥法（Orpha）
sometimes the manufacturers that was all
peace work they were a bit slapdash and
展开约4英尺的游戏装置
都是平行四边形，我想
peace work they were a bit slapdash and
so here you can see this mark shows it's
是吗
[音乐]
so here you can see this mark shows it's
it's number L this is where this tab
这是1887年的国际马戏团
Lothar meg和Orpha这是绝对的
it's number L this is where this tab
should have been stuck to but in actual
经典款均由平行四边形制成
像这样全部打开
should have been stuck to but in actual
fact whoever made it stuck it a bit
这些平行四边形向下折叠，它们
如果你得到的话，实际上要保持开放
fact whoever made it stuck it a bit
closer to the spine which meant that
他们以正确的顺序
那里你真的很棒
closer to the spine which meant that
then this side was also closer to the
[音乐]
spine which meant that the whole tent